<document><body>

<section name="What's this?">
<p>
	java.net sends a notification to the project owner whenever someone requests a new role, and you are supposed to process each one of them by using the java.net web interface.
	
	Oftentimes, you are happy to accept anyone as Observers, so this work quickly becomes tedious and boring.
</p><p>
	This tool automates this process. It reads such an e-mail and approve/decline/defer the request based on your policy file.
</p>
</section>
<section name="How to use">
<p>
	Run the program as follows:
</p><pre>
$ java -jar javaNetTasks.jar processRole [policyFile] &lt; [email]
</pre>
<p>
	See below for the syntax of the policy file.
</p><p>
	This tool is really useful in conjunction with procmail. You add the following  piece to your recipe:
</p>
<pre>
:0 c
* ^Subject: New role requested
* ^From: webmaster@dev.java.net
| java -jar /path/to/your/javaNetTasks.jar processRole /path/to/your/policyFile
</pre>
<p>
	With this set up, as soon as someone requests a role, his request will be processed immediately.
</p>
</section>

<section name="Policy file">
<p>
	A policy file is a simple text file that describes how you'd like to process role requests. Each line describes a condition and the action taken when the condition matches. For example, you write:
</p>
<pre>
# a comment line
myproject:*:Observer:APPROVE
*:*:Project Owner:DECLINE reason.txt
</pre>
<p>
	This example reads: <i>if anyone requests an observer role in myproject, approve him. But anyone requesting the project owner role in any of my project gets declined with the message specified in <tt>reason.txt</tt></i>
</p><p>
	Each line is separated by ':'. First three parts describe a condition, and the last part describes the action. The first part is the project name, or '*' to match to any project. The second part is the user name who requested a role. Again specify '*' to match anyone. The third part is the requested role. This can be also '*' to match any role. Everything is case sensitive.
</p><p>
	The last part specifies the action. It can be:
</p><ol>
	<li><b>"APPROVE"</b> to approve the request.</li>
	<li><b>"DECLINE file"</b> to decline the request. The contents of the specified file shall describe the reason (which will be sent to the person who requested a role.)</li>
	<li><b>"DEFER"</b> to do nothing, which means you'll have to process it manually</li>
</ol>
<p>
	Conditions are cheked in the order specified in the policy file.
	If no condition matches, no action will be taken.
</p>
<hr/>
<div align="right" style="font-size: smaller">
$Id: processRole.xml 84 2003-12-18 22:54:45Z kohsuke $
</div>
</section>
</body>
</document>
